--==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩影视 请访问 http://cmct.cc
影片压制: 犇犇    字幕制作: 犇犇
招募Q号: 76846146
演员:阿诺史瓦辛格
片名：魔鬼孩子王
潘妮洛普安蜜勒
对不起
Excuse me.
浑球
Shithead.
你不该来
You shouldn't be here.
起码叫价一千元 我尽可能抬价 你躲起来
I know. Ask for at least $1,000, okay? I'll get as much as I can. You hide.
他老婆带走儿子和几百万元 应该要一千元
His wife took his kid and a couple of million... and we won't get a thousand.
闭嘴 躲起来 我答应单独来
Shut up and stay hidden. I told him I was coming alone.
编剧：墨瑞赛林 赫雪温格 提摩西哈里斯
制片：伊凡瑞特曼 布莱恩格拉赛
克利先生 你好吗？
Hey, Mr. Crisp. How's it going?
导演：伊凡瑞特曼
你有我妻儿的消息？
You said you had information about my family.
是呀 我有
Yeah, yeah, I do.
好 说给我听
Well, let's have it.
你得花钱
Well, it's going to cost you.
一千块钱
Like $1,000?
这显然不是底价 750元也好
Okay, that's obviously not my final offer. 750 would be fine.
不仅是好
I mean, more than fine.
说给我听 我会好好赏你
Just tell me what you have, Danny... and I'll take good care of you.
好 这话很中听
Okay. That sounds fair.
上周我给高基跑腿 见到你前妻
I was doing a delivery for Corky last week out of state... and I ran into your ex.
她怎么样？
How'd she look?
很漂亮 克利先生
She looked great, Mr. Crisp. Yeah.
发型改了不过容貌值百万元
She changed her hair and stuff... but she looked like a million dollars.
其实她卷三百万元逃走
In fact, she looked like about $3 million.
她看见你没有？
Did she see you?
没有 我正换轮胎
No. I was changing a tire...
她过马路送她儿子上学
and suddenly, there she was across the street... taking her kid into this school.
我儿子
My boy?
他很好 很健康
Looked great. He looked very healthy.
定居的地方优美宽阔
It's a real nice, healthy place where they're living.
冬天下雪
It snows in winter there.
丹尼
Danny...
他们在那儿？
where are they?
在那所学校被我看到
At the school where I saw them...
爱莎利亚小学
Astoria Elementary School. That's...
奥勒冈州爱沙利亚镇
It's in Astoria, Oregon.
奥勒冈
Oregon.
有没有告诉别人？
All right. Did you tell anyone else this?
绝对没有
No. No way.
我不笨 克利先生
Hey, I'm not stupid, Mr. Crisp.
你不笨？
You're not?
丹尼
Danny.
Danny! No!
丹尼
Danny!
丹尼 起来
Danny! Get up!
不要丢下我自己死
Don't you die on me!
我没杀他
I didn't kill him. I didn't kill him.
克利杀的？
Was it Crisp?
不知道 没看见 我在纸箱里
I don't know. I didn't see anything.
你干什么？
What are you doing?
嗨 嗨 嗨
Hey, hey, hey!
住手
Stop it! Don't do that!
不要乱跑
Don't go anywhere.
放我走
Let me go!
让我同他分开
No! Let me off of him!
你做的发型我不喜欢
I don't like what you've done. I really don't like it.
真难看 令我呕气
It feels terrible, and it looks dreadful.
我已尽力
I'm trying my best.
还是不好
Maybe your best isn't good enough.
我回来了
I'm back.
你办事好快 轻而易举
Oh, great. Well, that was fast. It was easy.
妈 有令人兴奋的消息
I have some great, exciting, wonderful news, Mother.
孤冷 你老爱夸张
Oh, you always exaggerate, Cullen.
样样都说得美 什么好消息？
Everything is always great, terrific. So, what's so great?
我晓得他们藏身之地
I just found out where they're hiding.
当真？你晓得儿子下落？
Are you serious? You really know where he is?
修指甲？克利先生
Manicure, Mr. Crisp?
我怎么舍得回绝你？
Oh, how could I say no to you?
怎么回事？告诉我
Tell me. What's happened?
妈 这件事让我处理 我自有分寸
Just let me handle this myself, Mother. I know what I'm doing.
都在我掌握
Everything is under control.
我是警察
It's all right. I'm a police officer.
克利 束手就擒
Crisp, you're under arrest.
双手抱后脑 起立
Put your hands on your head and get up!
金霸 别再烦我
Kimble, not again!
双手抱头 手举起了
Your hands!
几时你才罢休？
They're up. When will you leave me alone?
把枪丢掉
Drop the gun!
对 把枪丢掉
我是警察 抓人犯
Hey, I'm a police officer. This is an arrest.
这个人是疯子
This man's crazy. Look at him.
他要杀我 制止他
He'll kill me. You're just going to stand there?
不准动
Freeze!
我是警察
I'm a cop!
约翰金霸警探 抓人犯
I'm Detective John Kimble.
我正在查询
This man is under arrest. I'm checking.
你不能持枪闯进来
You can't just walk in here and put a gun in my face.
我来此修指甲
I'm trying to get a manicure.
有人证
I have witnesses.
我也有人证
I have a witness, too.
这回是一级杀人罪
It's murder one this time.
你被我逮到了
Now you're mine.
那浑帐把我同死人铐在一起
The bastard handcuffed me to a dead man!
死人
A dead man!
坐下
Come on. Sit down.
丹尼可曾提到
Now, did Danny ever say
克利老婆的长相？
what Crisp's wife looked like? No.
可提到她用什么化名？
Did he ever say what name she was using in Oregon?
他没说 放我出去
He didn't say anything. Look, I just want to go home.
等指认凶嫌后我送你回家 还请你吃晚饭
After the lineup, I'll drive you home. I'll even buy you dinner.
我下厨做给你吃如何？我不要指认
I'll even cook you dinner. I'm not doing any lineup...
你能拿我怎么样？
and there ain't jack shit you can do about it!
我盯克利有四年了 不能放过
I've been after Crisp for four years... and she's letting my key witness walk away?
金霸 坐下
Kimble, sit down!
坐下 坐下
Sit down. - Sit. - Sit.
听着 他杀你的男友
Now listen to me. He killed your boyfriend.
只要你指一指
All you have to do is point your finger...
我们拿他下狱
and we can put him away for 30 years.
不是我的男友 萍水相逢
He wasn't my boyfriend. I hardly knew the guy.
我知道你在那边
I know you're in there.
知道你要什么
I know what you want, but you ain't getting it.
你休想如意
No lineup, no testimony.
带着手铐去你的
So shove your handcuffs up your ass!
放我出去
Now let me out of here!
别冲动
Slow down!
开门 让我出去
Open it and let me out!
奥哈拉 见过金霸
O'Hara, meet Kimble.
他盯克利很久了
Kimble's been on this a long time. Hi.
我来对付仙蒂
Let me take care of Cindy.
她会指认克利
She'll make Crisp. I guarantee it.
怎么对付？
What are you going to do...
把她铐在保险杠上
handcuff her to your car and take her for a ride?
我不会做晚饭给她吃
I'm not going to offer to cook her dinner.
金霸 等一下
Kimble, hold on a second. I...
你得多了解他 迫不及待
Difficult man. Got to get to know him. Oh, I can't wait.
嘿 宝贝
Hey, baby.
怎么叫他宝贝？
What you mean, " Hey, baby"?
厉害
Shit!
对不起 我忘了通报姓名
Oh, excuse me. I forgot to introduce myself.
我叫约翰金霸
My name is John Kimble...
深爱我的车子
and I love my car.
我帮你看守车子
I'll keep an eye on it for you.
你的车漂亮
You got a beautiful ride.
我不出手算他走运
Shit. Who does he think he is? He's lucky I didn't kick his ass.
开门
Open up.
你不能进来
You can't come in.
谢谢你
Thank you.
他妈什么事？
What the fuck?
好了…
All right...
席散了 大家回去
party's over. Everyone go home.
下回在我家聚会
Next time, my place.
你是谁？
So who are you, man?
要老命
Shit!
我无扫人家的兴
I'm the party-pooper.
嘿 仙蒂
Hi, Cindy.
我坐下你可在意？
Do you mind if I sit down?
不敢 老兄 请坐
No. Sit down, man.
又见你真好
Oh, it's so nice to see you again.
你来干什么 浑蛋？
What are you doing here, you asshole?
你骂脏话我不喜欢
Cindy, I don't like you using foul language...
你有气质
not a classy girl like you.
你没别的事好干？
Don't you have anything better to do?
你不明白 我没别的事
You don't understand. I have nothing else to do...
而且也没别处可去
and I have nowhere else to go.
干嘛瞪着我？
Why are you staring at me like that?
仙蒂 我喜欢你
I like you, Cindy.
要常在你左右
I'm going to be around you a lot...
日日夜夜不分周末假日
days, nights, weekends, holidays.
你不可以
No. No, you can't.
可以
Yes, I can.
我要守着你 天长地久
I'm going to hang out with you until the end of time.
快上去
All right, move it in.
快
Let's go.
站在号码上
Step onto the numbers.
面向前方
Face front.
两手自然下垂
Everybody, hands to your side.
就是那个瘪三
That's the creep.
谁？
Who? Number five.
五号 就是他
That's him.
好 很好
Good. Very good.
将你收押直到出庭受审
Mr. Crisp, you will be remanded into custody until your trial.
法警 押犯人下去
Bailiff, remove the prisoner.
别说话 放轻松 我来处理 放心
Shh. Don't say anything. Just take it easy. I'll take care of it. Trust me.
你可有办法？
You know what to do?
我是你娘对不对？
I'm your mother, aren't I?
我跟我的朋友谈
Mind if I talk to my friend a little bit?
律师不在我不跟你谈
I'm not talking to anybody without my lawyer.
律师在里面
He's right in here.
供出毒品来源
You give me the names of your drug suppliers and distributors...
我找法官讲情 说你这凶手听话肯合作
and I'll tell the judge what a nice, cooperative killer you are.
陪审不会听那吸毒女子的话 判我有罪
You think the jury's going to convict me on the testimony of that junkie?
你的话也许对
You could be right.
可是你老婆呢？
But what about your wife?
可记得她？
You remember her?
卷走你贩毒的昧心钱
All that hard-earned drug money she stole from you?
盗走多少钱？
How much was it...
三百万元？
$3 million?
她出庭作证更有效
I bet she would make a much better witness.
金霸 你盯我耗了几年 为了什么？
Kimble, you've wasted years chasing after me... and what has it gotten you, hmm?
什么都没
Nothing.
不为什么
I'll be out in a week...
不久我就自由 你仍旧吃便当
and you'll still be eating take-out food in that dump you live in.
金霸 我看透你了
Yeah, I know all about you, Kimble.
少了我你顿失生活的目标
Without me, you wouldn't even have a life.
我老婆为了钱遗弃我
My old lady left 'cause of the money.
你老婆眼里容不下你而离开
Yours left because she just couldn't stand the sight of you.
个子小胃口那么大？
I've never seen anyone so little eat so much.
我患低血糖 若不经常吃会发狂
Yeah, I know. I'm hypoglycemic. If I don't eat regularly... I get a little nuts.
你祖籍那里？
So... where you from?
奥地利
Austria.
当警察多久了
How long you been a cop?
十二年
I been a cop for 12 years.
父亲和兄长当警察 我妈当警察的老婆
My father was a cop... my brother was a cop... my mother was a cop's wife.
我没有嗜好 有好消息
And I have no hobbies.
明天你二人飞到波特兰
You two are booked on the first flight to Portland tomorrow.
找克利的老婆以豁免权
Locate Crisp's wife and offer her immunity
交换她出庭作证
in exchange for her testimony against him.
奥哈拉汉 别见怪 这件案子我要独自办
No offense to O'Hallahan... but this is my case, and I work alone.
独来独往改观了
He works alone. Not anymore.
她要扮幼稚园老师代课卧底
She's going in undercover as a substitute kindergarten teacher.
这差使你不合
Not exactly a job for you.
我干警察之前当过老师
I used to be a teacher. We'll be fine.
我做什么？
What do I do?
她找小孩 你找母亲和脏款
She locates the kid... you find the mother and the cash...
克利终生坐牢在监狱制牌照
and Crisp spends his life making license plates.
一路平安
Bon voyage.
金霸 我姓奥哈拉
Oh, and, Kimble, the name's O'Hara.
他老婆17岁的照片 本名瑞雪梅雅
OK. Here's the wife at 17. Real name's Rachel Myatt.
密苏里人 当过啦啦队长
She's from Hannibal, Missouri, class of '76.
高中交响乐团小提琴手
Cheerleader, first violin in the school orchestra...
垒球队长
captain of the girls' softball team.
立志要旅游 体验人生结交朋友
Her ambition was " To travel... experience life...
结交克利之流？
and meet interesting people." Like Crisp.
好的
Okay.
别激动 不要意气用事
Relax. Don't let him get to you.
她高中毕业后十年的照片
That's her 10 years later.
照相技术真高 她的双亲呢
It's a great shot of an ear. You get in touch with her parents?
都死了
They're both dead.
儿子是她仅有的亲人
The only relative she's got left is the kid.
嗨
Hey.
警方仅有他这张照片
Okay. This is the only picture we have of him.
孤冷二世 三个月大
Cullen Jr., aged 3 months.
真管用
That helps much.
我只弄到这张照片
It's the best I could do.
吃早餐？拜托
Breakfast, sir? Ma'am?
不吃
Please. No. No, no.
头一回拒吃
That's a first.
我刚想到
Listen, I was just thinking.
我们应该彼此多了解
Maybe we should take a wild stab at getting to know each other before we
才好冒充夫妻
have to pretend we're married.
想了解什么？我们结婚多久了？
What do you want to know? How long have we been married?
很久了 彼此不理睬很正常
A long time. People won't expect us to talk much to each other.
杂志给我 我也要看
I want to read it, too.
住手
Stop it. Please?
拜托给我 给我看
Let me take a look.
过来
Hey, come here.
要是你不停止捣蛋
If you don't stop screwing around back there...
要你像这支铅笔
this is what I'll do with you.
噢
Ohh.
怎么回事？不知道
What's the matter? I don't know.
怎么了？胃不舒服
I just don't feel so good.
饿不饿？
You hungry?
马上要上洗手间
I got to get out of here right now.
移开你的树干腿 免得我吐在你身上
Get those tree stumps out of my way before I vomit all over them.
你太太要不要紧？
Is your wife okay, sir?
拿什么时候比？
Compared to what?
也许玉米饼吃坏肚子
Maybe it was the burrito.
或者是香肠不卫生
Or it could've been the sausages.
蟹肉沙拉和甜甜圈 不会有问题
I don't think it was the crab salad. It couldn't have been the doughnuts.
对不起
Excuse me.
闹肠胃真可恶
Oh, I hate feeling like this.
我也憎恶
I hate it, too.
呃
Uh-oh.
什么？
Uh-oh what? Uh-oh...
停车
pull over.
马上停？是呀 快点
Now? Yeah. Please hurry.
厕所钥匙
The key! Give me the key!
要不要帮忙？
Do you need a hand?
你好吗？很好
You okay? I'm fine.
不要紧
I'll be fine.
明天九点才上课
Class starts at 9:00 in the morning.
到时就好了
I'll be fine.
你的气色好多了
You look much better already.
幼稚园 六岁儿童
Oh. Kindergarten, 6-year-olds.
所以我辞掉教职
That's why I quit teaching, you know.
别人的小孩烦死我了
I got so sick of other people's kids.
教下去 只有自己都不想生孩子
I was afraid that I'd never want to have any of my own.
我有个儿子
I have a son.
十三岁了
He's 13.
我记得他五岁的样子
I remember when he was 5.
他跟着母亲和继父
He lives with his mother and stepfather. Aah!
怎么回事？
What's the matter?
那是什么东西？
What... is... that?
忘了跟你讲
Oh, excuse me. I forgot to tell you.
我养的雪貂
This is my ferret.
不会咬人 放心
He doesn't bite. Don't worry.
来吧 出来
Come on. Come on out.
弄个累赘 真是愈帮愈忙
This is all I need... an obstacle.
弄个累赘给我
A goddamn obstacle. He sends me an obstacle. Here.
我的天
Oh, God.
放心
Don't worry.
我一定能代课
I'm going to make it.
只要歇一会儿
I just need a minute.
一分钟可以准备好 只要
I'll be ready in just a minute. I just got...
我的天
Oh, God.
这样打扮如何？
How do I look?
取下手枪
Take off the gun.
好主意
That's a good idea.
那些小杂种会把你生吞活剥
The little bastards are going to eat you alive.
你安心养病吧
Get some rest, and don't worry.
卧底密探我干很久了
I've been working undercover for a long time.
六岁孩童能有多大能耐？
They're 6-year-olds. How much trouble can they be?
再想想
On second thought...
还是带枪的好
take the gun.
马修
Matthew...
你打珍妮所以我要你见校长
I sent you to the principal's office because you punched Jenny.
我知道 她毒死你的大颠鼠
I know. She poisoned your hamsters.
她跟我说了 还道歉
She told me all about it... and she's very sorry.
我不相信你 我道歉
And I'm sorry that I didn't believe you.
但不能打人 可是她
- But you shouldn't punch people. - But she...
我知道
I know!
金宝先生 史校长有请
Mr. Kimble, Miss Schlowski will see you now.
我们回课堂
Let's go back to class.
有何指教？
Can I help you?
我是约翰金霸 新来的老师
I'm John Kimble, your new kindergarten teacher.
我们等的是奥哈拉小姐
We were expecting a Miss O'Hara.
安排有所变更
There's been a change of plan.
这学期剩四周
Four weeks into the new semester...
督学要我更换赫老师
my superintendent told me I had to replace Mrs. Hagley...
她有廿五年幼教经验
a kindergarten teacher of 25 years' experience...
却要由密探顶替也不说原委
with an undercover police officer... and he wouldn't even tell me why.
我想你也不愿说内情吧？
I don't suppose you would do me the courtesy of filling me in.
我不能说
I can't do that.
你不能说
Oh. You can't do that.
我会监视你
I'm watching you.
我只消对家长说 你是警方的人
All I have to do is tell my parents that you're with the police...
他们会急忙接孩子走 要学校关门
and they'll yank their kids out of this school so fast... we'd have to close.
为了学童的安全 我不惜关门
And don't you think I won't if I feel my children are in any danger.
学童没有危险
They're not in danger.
我猜想你有教学经验吧？
I assume you have some teaching experience.
没有怎么会派我来？
They wouldn't have sent me otherwise.
在门口等一下
Just wait here a minute.
大家坐在地毯上
Everybody sit down on the carpet!
小朋友早安 早安 史校长
Good morning, everyone. Good morning, Miss Schlowski.
你们的老师赫小姐 有要事出远门
Your teacher, Mrs. Hagley had to go on an important trip.
上那去？
Where'd she go?
那不重要
That doesn't matter.
她死了？
Did she die?
没死 罗威 她去看别人
No, Lowell. She went to see someone.
别人死了？
Did they die?
没死 罗威
No, Lowell.
人都要死
Everyone dies, you know.
我知道 但是要活很久才死
I know, but not for a long, long time.
赫老师回来之前
Now, until Mrs. Hagley comes back...
我们特别请了人帮忙代课
we have someone special to help.
这位是金霸老师 你们的新老师
This is Mr. Kimble... your new kindergarten teacher.
大家一起说
Now, let's everybody say,
金霸老师 早安
"Good morning, Mr. Kimble."
早安 金霸老师
Good morning, Mr. Kimble.
早安
Good morning.
都交给你了
They're all yours.
我会监视你
I'll be watching you.
嗨
Hi.
大家好
How are you?
来到这里很高兴
I'm very happy to be here.
首先我要认识大家
First I would like to just get to know you.
肃静
Quiet.
我要问你们一些问题
I'm going to ask you a bunch of questions.
你们要立刻回答
I want to have them answered immediately.
有多少人在爱沙利亚出生？
How many of you were born in Astoria?
举手
Raise your hands. Let's see them.
好吧 嗯
Okay, hmm.
谁在爱镇以外出生
Now, anyone that was not born in Astoria...
譬如加州 举手
somewhere outside like California... raise your hands.
是的
Yes.
我要上洗手间
I need to go to the bathroom.
好 你去
Okay. You can go.
男生有小鸡鸡 女生有小屁屁
Boys have a penis. Girls have a vagina.
谢谢你的情报
Thanks for the tip.
是？
Yes?
我要上厕所解不开吊带扣
I need to go to the bathroom... and I can't get these things off.
我找人帮你解 马上来
I'll get someone to help you. I'll be right back, okay?
你们知道"e"字母
You've learned that the " e" is often silent
接另一母音则常常不发音
when it immediately follows another vowel.
抄这些字然后读
Now write and say these words...
哦 嗯…
Oh, um...
下课 嗯 凯瑟琳…
class, uh, Catherine...
凯瑟琳 请你代一下
can you take over for me, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
"E"是字母表中第五个字母
"E" is the fifth letter of the alphabet.
有何指教？
Yes, can I help you?
我有点困难
I have a problem.
报告老师 我的尿好急
Mr. Kimble... I need to go real bad.
第一天？是的
First day? Yes.
我来照应她 谢谢
I'll take care of her. Thank you.
幼稚园像海洋变化莫测
You know, kindergarten is like the ocean.
一转身学童就造反
Don't turn your back on it.
我的学生还好 别耽心
They're okay. Don't worry.
都在我掌握中
Everything is under control.
不好
No.
小妖怪
Monsters.
你拿这个干什么？
What are you doing with this?
你不出面制止？
Aren't you going to break it up?
不要 这样再闹两天包他请辞
No. Two more days of this... and he'll quit.
闭嘴
Shut up!
Shut up.
闭嘴
Shut up!
不行 不要哭
No. Don't start this.
糟了
Oh, no...
啊哈
Aah!
注意
Attention!
这是班上新的吉祥兽
This is your new class mascot.
你的狗怎么了？
What happened to your dog?
不是狗
This is not a dog.
是雪貂
This is a ferret.
雪貂是什么？
What's a ferret?
这就是雪貂
That's a ferret. Oh!
被它咬伤会得狂犬病死跷跷
If he bites you, you get rabies and die.
没这回事 它不咬人
No. That's not true. He never bites.
可以摸它？
Can I pet him?
可以 一个一个来摸
Sure, but one at a time, okay?
好 下一个 过来
Good. Okay, next one. Come on.
很好
Yes. Good.
Yeah.
很好 我们开心的玩
Good. Now we're having fun.
什么意思？
What's that supposed to mean?
赫老师比你好多了
Mrs. Hagley is a lot better than you.
是吗？
Is she?
真的比我好？
Is she really?
我妈也在学校教书
My mom's a teacher in this school...
她也比你好多了
and she's a lot better than you, too.
很好
Great.
星期一晚上我妈当家教
On Monday nights, my mom tutors
昆恩太太看顾我也比你强
and Mrs. Quinn takes care of me. She's better than you, too.
很好
Great.
我的游泳老师 棒球教练
And Frankie, my swimming teacher... and Gus, my T-ball coach,
也都比你强
are better than you, too.
谢谢你说老实话
I really appreciate your honesty.
可认识不比我强的人？
You happen to know someone that's not better than me?
不认识比你差的人
I don't know that many people.
约翰？
John?
你回来了？
Are you there?
情形如何？
How did it go?
走开
Go away.
上课有这么顺利？
It went that well, huh?
明天你接手
You take over tomorrow.
暴露身份？
And blow our cover?
我不能接
Can't do it.
他们好可怕
They're horrible.
那还用说
Tell me about it.
他患同性恋
He's gay.
正常男人那会教幼稚园？
What kind of a man teaches kindergarten? He's obviously gay.
男老师令我不能适应
A male kindergarten teacher isn't what I'm used to.
莎曼珊叫他"巨人"
Samantha calls him "The giant."
他来了 在那儿？
There he is. Where, honey?
天啊 你的新老师？
Holy cow, is that your new teacher? Yeah.
我的天
Oh, my God.
- 你干什么？- 我没有化妆
- What are you doing? - I'm not wearing makeup.
我们都没化妆
None of us are.
你有老公 邋遢没关系
You're married. You're allowed to look like slobs.
要听话 我会接你放学
Be good. I'll be back to pick you up.
金霸老师 早安
Good morning, Mr. Kimble.
早安
Good morning.
我说过他高大
I told you he was big.
去同小朋友玩
Play with the kids, honey.
我叫姬莲 席维斯的母亲
Hi. I'm Jillian, Sylvester's mom. Do you have a minute?
耽误一分钟同你谈谈？
I'd like to speak with you.
好呀
Sure.
请坐 谢谢
Please. Thank you.
男人教幼稚园 少见
A male kindergarten teacher. That's unusual.
你不是本地人
You're not from around here, are you?
不是
No. I'm not.
我也不是
Neither am I. Huh.
总之
Anyway...
嗯…
um...
小有问题
I have a small problem.
是？
Yes?
席维斯的父亲不跟我们住
You see, Sylvester's father doesn't live with us anymore...
我一直为席维斯耽心
and I've just been worried about Sylvester.
最近他举止乖张
He's been acting a little strange lately...
行为有异
You know, doing odd things.
什么异状？
Like what?
玩洋娃娃着了迷
Well, it seems that's he's becoming a little obsessed with playing with dolls.
行为怪异
You know, it's weird.
我能帮忙 真的？
I think I can help you with that.
他利用玩洋娃娃 窥看女生裙底
Really? He uses the dolls to look up girls' skirts.
昨天我见他窥看
I caught him doing it yesterday.
那我就放心了
Oh. Oh, well, that's a relief.
不过我会留意他 谢谢
But I'll keep an eye on him, okay? Thank you.
席维斯有没有见父亲？
Does Sylvester ever see his father?
没有 打两岁起就没有
No. No, not since he was 2.
他父亲住在加州
His father lives in California.
相隔遥远
That is far away. Mm-hmm.
把他的姓名电话告诉我
Well, if you give me his name and number... I could talk to him
我来请他多关注儿子
about taking more interest in his son.
谢谢你的好意但不用了
That's very kind, but I don't think so.
席维斯是否难适应？
But it's tough on Sylvester, don't you think?
不会
No. No, what's tough on Sylvester
他父亲另有男人才令他难受
is his father left us for another man.
金霸先生 你结婚没有？
Are you married, Mr. Kimble?
没有
No, I'm not.
妈 他没有结婚
He's not married, Mom!
欢迎 爱镇是单亲家庭之都
Welcome to Astoria... the single-parent capital of America.
谢谢你抽空
Thank you for your time.
本人谨宣誓
I pledge allegiance
忠于
to the flag
美利坚合众团国旗
of the United States of America...
暨国旗代表之共合
and to the republic for which it stands...
一统之国家得天庇佑
one nation, under God...
不可分裂
indivisible...
人人自由平等
with liberty and justice for all.
餐盒都是你的？
Are these all your lunches?
你偷吃别人的午餐？
You mean you eat other people's lunches?
嘴巴停
Stop it!
现在要做有趣的事
Now we're going to do something extremely fun.
来玩游戏 名称是"我爸爸是谁？做什么事"
We're going to play a game called... "Who is my daddy and what does he do?"
是？
Yes?
你爸爸是消防员？
Is your daddy a fireman?
可能好壮 是不是摔角手？
He's probably big. Is he a wrestler?
是不是棒球教练？
A basketball coach? No, no.
怎么回事？
What's the matter?
头疼
I have a headache.
可能是长脑瘤
It might be a tumor.
不是长脑瘤
It's not a tumor!
根本不是长瘤
It's not a tumor at all.
我是要你们告诉我
What I meant was...
你们的爸爸是谁？做什么事？
you tell me who is your daddy and what does he do?
哦
Oh.
懂不懂？从你开始
Get it? We start right here. You.
我爸爸修理汽车 笨女人撞坏的车
My dad repairs cars driven by women who are pinheads.
车祸以后我爸爸什么都不做
My dad doesn't do anything since the crash.
我爸爸拿钱给没有钱的人
My dad gives money to people that doesn't have money...
那些人拿钱去用
then people use that money...
把多余的钱还回来
then they give other money back
然后把同样多的钱 还给我爸爸
and they give the same amount of money back to my dad.
我爸不同我们住 他住在纽约开计程车
My dad doesn't live with us anymore. He lives in New York and drives a taxi.
我妈希望他快点死
My mom hopes he's going to die real soon.
我爸成天看电视
My dad watches TV all day long.
我爸用电脑办公
My dad works on computers...
他是公司的老板
and he's, um, the boss of his company...
满嘴满脸长胡子
and, um, he has a mustache and a beard.
嗯 嗯
Mm-hmm.
呀
Yeah.
头发却没那么多
He doesn't have that much hair because...
他的脑袋瓜好大 戴不下帽子
and he... his head is so big that he can't wear any hats.
我爸离婚了 我妈离婚了
My dad's divorced. My mom's divorced.
我爸是精神医师
My dad, um, is a psychologist...
治疗感情受创伤 或是丧失感情的人 完毕
and he helps people that are hurt or lost their feelings... and, um, that's it.
我们的妈说爸爸是性爱机器
Our mom says that our dad is a real sex machine.
很好
Good.
我不知爸做什么事
I don't know what my dad does.
好久没见到他了
I haven't seen him in a long time.
他住在法国
He lives in France.
我爸是妇科医师
My dad is a gynecologist...
成天看屁屁
and he looks at vaginae all day long.
谢谢 很好
Thank you. Very good.
下一位 背朝我的是谁？
Okay. Next, uh... What's his name with his back to me?
他叫柴克苏利文 不跟人讲话
His name's Zach Sullivan. He doesn't like anyone to talk to him.
他脑筋"秀斗"
He's a poo-poo head.
他的脸丑陋
He's a poo-poo face.
他是狗屎牛粪
He's a ca-ca poo-poo.
他是便便 便便
He's a poo-poo ca-ca.
- 便便 便便 - 便便 便便
- Poo-poo ca-ca! - Poo-poo ca-ca!
安静 不要说了
Quiet. That's enough.
柴克
Hey, Zach.
爸爸教你玩这种游戏
Did your daddy teach you this game?
柴克 跟大家一起玩 更有趣味
Come on, Zach. Let's all play together. It's so much more fun.
不要烦我
Leave me alone!
什么声音？
What's that?
火警
It's a fire alarm!
快点 大家一起 快点
Come on, come on. Everyone together! Come on.
我身上着火了
I'm on fire!
大家在一起 我身上着火了
Come on. All together! I'm on fire!
成一路排整齐
Very straight. Very straight.
大家在一起 听话 大家在一起
Come on, come on. Get all together. Everything together. Come on.
快走 安静 安静
Come on. Quiet. Quiet! Come on.
幼稚园同学加入我们真高兴
Shh! Quiet. Well, we're all glad the kindergarten class could join us.
四分钟 你们应该惭愧
That's four minutes. You should be ashamed of yourselves.
其他各班级使用的时间 有进步
All the other grades... your times were an improvement...
不过还不够迅速
but they're still not good enough.
我非常失望
I'm very disappointed.
好 回学校去
All right, let's get back into school.
苏太太
Mrs. Sullivan!
医生诊断为感冒
So the doctor says it's a stomach flu.
我很好 不用忌嘴
I'm fine. I can eat anything I want.
我们找餐厅
Let's find a restaurant.
能不能谈公事？当然
Can we talk business?
我那班有14个男童
There are 14 boys in the classroom.
有三个可疑 排除了一个 这是他照片 听进去没有？
So far I have three possible suspects, one likely. Here's a picture. You listening?
我听到了
I'm listening.
他叫柴克苏利文
His name's Zach Sullivan. What do you think?
长得可爱
He's cute.
怎么没有餐厅？
Doesn't anybody eat around here?
长得酷似克利 你看
Listen, he's a dead ringer for Crisp. Look.
也许是 约翰 我饿了
Maybe. Come on, John. I'm hungry.
是 订二人桌 谢谢
A table for two. Thank you very much.
我要两分热狗 两客？
Two hot dogs. Two hot dogs?
金宝先生 金宝先生 多明尼
Mr. Kimble! Mr. Kimble!
妈 他来了 多明尼
Dominic. It's him, Mom.
我叫乔伊丝
Joyce.
你好 乔伊丝 多明尼是个好帮手
Hello, Joyce. Dominic has been a great help.
他是个好孩子
He's a good kid.
那个是谁？
Who's that?
谁
Who?
她是谁？
Her.
那个 那是
Oh, that? Uh, that is, uh...
是他妹子
I am his sister.
真的？教人猜不到
Oh, really? I wouldn't have guessed.
请原谅家兄 他没礼貌
You have to excuse my brother. He has no manners.
我叫乌苏拉 从奥地利来 很高兴见到你们
My name is Ursula. Wonderful to meet you. I'm visiting here from Austria.
乔伊丝波尔马利 跟约翰同事
I'm Joyce Paulmarie. I work at John's school.
这是多明尼 嗨 多明尼
Ah. And this is Dominic.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
彼此
坐一桌好不好？
Would you like to join us for dinner?
- 好啊 - 不用
- No. - Ja.
好呀
Ja.
好 好极了
Yes, of course. That would be great.
四人桌
Hi. There will be four of us.
27号桌
Table 27.
为什么冒充我妹子？
Why did you tell her you were my sister?
别紧张 屠夫 我是爱情神医
Relax, butch. The love doctor is here.
到我这儿 我先点菜
Come to me. I want to start.
我要牛小排加洋芋泥 大盘青菜沙拉
Okay. I want a rib eye steak with mashed potatoes and a large green salad.
等一下 我先点酱淋鸡翅
Oh, no. Wait a minute. I want to start with the spicy chicken wings.
不是小鸡翅吧？
Are they the tiny ones without meat?
不是 是大鸡翅
Actually, it's quite a large serving.
手臂结实
Ah, good. Ooh, good arms.
还要大碗杂烩
And a large bowl of the clam chowder.
蓝梅派冰淇淋甜点
Uh, and the blueberry pie with ice cream for dessert.
我喜欢他们的腔调
I like how they talk.
我想认识家长有些却回避我
I've been trying to get to know the parents... but some of them are avoiding me.
有些家长是这样
Some of them are like that. It's a strange town that way...
新定居的尤其怪异
especially with new arrivals.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
我认为迁居小镇的人
I think a lot of people that come to small towns
都是逃亡
are trying to get away from something
或是避祸
or they're hiding something.
比方什么？
Like what?
比方说 你为何来此？
Well, for example, what brought you here?
这里有幼稚园老师的缺
Me? Well, there was an opening for a kindergarten teacher.
为何要教幼稚园？
Yeah, but what made you become a kindergarten teacher?
有点儿不寻常
I mean, it is a bit unusual.
约翰是与众不同
John is a bit unusual.
你是不同
Well... You are.
我生于奥地利
I was born in Austria.
家父当教师
My father was a teacher.
家母当老师 乌苏拉也是
My mother was a teacher. So is Ursula. Ja.
我们奥地利人 子女继承父母之业
We have a tradition in Austria where we follow the footsteps of our parents.
这所以现在来到美国
So when I moved to this country...
我曾经在亚利桑那州教地理和体育
I taught geography and physical education in Arizona...
后来当篮球教练 教罗德岛的女孩
and then I coached basketball at an all-girls school in Rhode Island, but...
不过以上工作都不愉快
none of it made me really happy.
为什么不愉快？对 为什么不愉快？
Why weren't you happy? Ja. Why weren't you happy?
厌倦了教青少年
Well, I got tired of teaching teenagers... because by the time they came to me...
对青少年我没什么助益
I felt there wasn't much I could do with them.
幼稚园学习阶段才重要
I realized that the real action is in kindergarten.
教幼稚园多久了？
How long have you been teaching kindergarten?
第二天
It's my second day.
哦
Oh.
对不起
Ooh, excuse me, but it's good.
不过好吃 好吃
It is good.
再次感谢 很愉快
Thanks again.
非常谢谢 很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
再见
Thank you. Bye.
我很开心 是呀 彼此
I had a great time. Ja, me, too.
金霸 你有搞头了
Well, Kimble, I think you scored.
哇 哇 哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
你胡扯些什么
What are you talking about? I'm only interested in her
基于同事关心 我才对他感兴趣
because she works at the school.
她对亲子都熟悉
She knows the children and the parents.
你若再死板一点 可当做冲浪板
If you were any stiffer... we could take you surfing.
你喜欢她 顾忌什么？
Now, I know you like that woman. What is your problem?
我代你的差使
The only problem I've got is that I'm doing your job.
应该是你清除漆污
You should be cleaning up the paint
读小熊采买的故事
and reading stories about bears that go shopping.
卡在你的任务上 你卡住了？
I'm stuck with your job. Yeah. You are.
我是卡住
That's right. I am.
过几天你就能脱身
Look, you're going to be out of here in a few days.
刚才你还说有好主意
You told me yourself you had a few good leads.
不久就能再抓毒虫和凶手了
You'll be back dealing with junkies and murderers in no time.
他们逼得我团团转
They're pushing me around.
谁？
Who?
小孩子
The kids.
淘气不听话
They're walking all over me.
听我说
Listen, Kimble.
拿出警察的手段来对付
You got to handle this like any other police situation.
怀着惧意进教室 你死定了
You walk into it showing fear... you're dead...
小孩看得出你怕了
and those kids know you're scared.
不怕
No fear.
今天玩新的游戏
Today we're going to play a new fun game.
叫做"警察学校"
It's called " police school."
我当警长
I'm going to be your sheriff.
你们当受训学员
You're going to be my deputy trainees.
来吧
Come on.
不要叫苦
Stop whining.
你们软弱 缺少纪律
You kids are soft. You lack discipline.
你们在我掌握中 属于我
Well, I've got news for you. You are mine now. You belong to me!
妈妈不在这里 帮你们擦屁股
You're not going to have your mommies here to wipe your tushies.
锻炼肌肉的时候到了
Oh, no. It's time to turn this mush into muscles.
再也不准嚷着上厕所
No more complaining. No more, " I have to go to the bathroom."
没有厕所
There is no bathroom!
受训第一件事要学习
Now, the first thing the deputy trainees have to learn
一听到哨音就静止
is to freeze whenever you hear this.
再听到哨音
Now, the next time you hear this whistle...
每个人拿一件玩具
each one of you get one toy.
几件？
How many?
一件
One!
很好 拿到地毯上
Good. Then bring it back to the carpet...
动作要快 预备？
pronto. Ready?
等一下
Wait for it.
等哨音响 坐下
Wait for it. Sit down.
预备？
Ready?
起 快 拿玩具
Go quickly. Get your toy.
走 去拿玩具 动作快
Go. Go for it. Yes. Very fast.
好 快 带玩具回到地毯上
Good. Quickly. Bring the toy back to the carpet.
拿了回地毯上
Bring it back to the carpet.
快 快 快 回地毯上 快
Quick, quick, quick. Back to the carpet. Quickly.
恩玛
Emma.
艾玛…
Emma...
带玩具到地毯上
take your toy to the carpet.
我不是警察 是公主
I'm not a policeman. I'm a princess.
带玩具到地毯上
Take your toy back to the carpet.
我不是警察 是公主
I'm not a policeman! I'm a princess.
带回地毯上
Take it back!
好嘛
All right.
很好
Very good.
做得好
You did very well.
再玩一种游戏
Now we're going to play another game.
听到哨音两响
When you hear two whistle blows...
每人把玩具归原位 回到地毯上 几响？
take your toy back where you got it and come right back. How many whistle blows?
两响 两响
Two! Two!
很好 准备好
Good. Ready?
起
Go.
回到地毯上
Come on. Come right back to the carpet.
这招管用 好极了
Yes. It works. This is great.
快一点 加油
Faster, faster. Come on.
妙极了 这招奏效 漂亮
Yes. Come back. Terrific. This is working. Wait.
我是说你们是好警察
I mean, you're very good deputies.
警长觉得光荣
Your sheriff is proud of you.
一 二 三 四 一 二 三 四
1, 2, 3, 4.
一 二 三 四
等等 带我去
Wait! Take me.
下 上 下
Down. Up. Down.
是的 是的 没错
Yes, yes, yes!
你已经得到了它
You've got it.
是的 万达 好
Yes, Wanda. Good.
挺好
Very good.
大圈 大圆圈
Big circles. Big circles.
好
Good.
现在重复做同样的动作
Now do the same thing. Way back.
和向下的大圆圈
And down in big circles.
大圈
Big circles.
是的
Yes.
火警演习
This is a fire drill!
火警演习 跑到门口
This is a fire drill. Run to the door.
多明尼 别忘了雪貂
Dominic, don't forget Ferret.
对 火警演习
Yes. It's a fire drill. Come on.
慢得可怕
Oh, this is terrible.
来吧 来吧
Come on. Come on.
二十九  二十九
29 29
三十
三十一
三十二
三十三
再做一下 仰卧起坐
One more. Come on. Down and up. Yes!
柴克得胜 为他鼓掌
Yes! Zach is the winner.
来吧 你们这些家伙
Come on, you guys.
齐步走 二 三 四
March, 2, 3, 4.
前进 二 三 四
手臂摆动 二 三 四
Swing your arms. 2, 3, 4.
手臂抬高 二 三 四
Swing them high. 2, 3, 4.
一 二 三 四
1, 2, 3, 4.
哇塞
Wow.
一 二 三 四
1, 2, 3, 4!
读书写字作算数
Reading, writing, arithmetic.
读书写字作算术
Reading, writing, arithmetic!
功课太多倒胃口
Too much homework makes me sick.
Too much homework makes me sick!
考试及格时
When it's time to pass the test...
幼稚园里顶呱呱
kindergarten is the best.
Kindergarten is the best.
耶
Yay!
咿呀咿呀哟
E-I-E-I-O
农场里面有只鸭
And on that farm he had a duck
咿呀咿呀哟
E-I-E-I-O
拿牛奶喝
All right. Take your milk.
喝了高又壮
It makes you big and strong.
金霸老师 讲故事时间
It's story time, Mr. Kimble. All right.
我们要听这个
We all like this one... and if you read us a story now...
现在讲这故事大家会睡觉
everybody will go to sleep. All right.
"我们小时候"
我曾念这本给儿子听
I used to read this to my son.
他叫什么名字？
What's his name?
谁？
Who?
你儿子
Your son.
他叫亚历
Oh, Alex is his name.
他在那里？
Where is he?
同他妈住
He lives with his mother.
是这样
You see, his mother and I...
他妈和我
we are...
离婚了 我晓得 离婚是什么？
Divorced. I know. What's a divorce?
就是你爸住别处
It's when your daddy lives someplace else
有时候来带你去玩
and comes over to take you places...
你妈骂他赖帐
and your mommy says he's a deadbeat.
就是爸爸不想再看到儿子
No. It's when the daddy doesn't want to see his little boy anymore.
不是不想
That's not what it is.
为什么你不想看儿子？
Why don't you want to see your little boy?
他不乖？
Was he bad?
不是 他不是不乖
No, he was not bad.
完全不是他的错
It wasn't his fault at all.
是这样 他妈和我
You see...
我们合不来
his mommy and I, we just nev...
坐下好不好？
Just sit down, okay?
我来念 你们都躺下
Let me just start reading. Why don't you all lie down?
好
Okay.
很好 休息
Good. And rest.
假如你小鸟住在高处
"If you were a bird and lived on high
风吹过来你随风翱翔
you'd lean on the wind when the wind came by.
你对飘送你的风说
You'd say to the wind when it took you away...
今天我要去的地方
That's where I wanted to go today.
上那儿去？我不清楚
Where am I going? I don't quite know.
人上那儿去有什么关系？
What does it matter where people go?
到森林里野风信子花开处
Down to the wood where the bluebells grow.
那里都好 随便何方
Anywhere. Anywhere.
我不知道
I don't know.
咦
Huh!
嗨
Hi.
你好
不是故意惊吓你
I didn't mean to startle you.
一定是我睡着了
I must have dozed off.
想不到你能哄他们睡着
I can't believe you got them all to sleep.
我令他们劳动
I worked them hard.
不知你可愿赏光
I was wondering if...
明天到我家吃晚饭
you'd like to come to my place for dinner tomorrow night.
我愿意
I would like that.
是的
Yes.
好 这是方向指南
Great. Well, here are the directions.
六点半至七点
How about 6:30, 7:00?
好呀
That would be fine.
怎么了？
What?
嗯
Um...
你长胡子了
You... You've got a little mustache.
喝牛奶沾到
Oh, it must be from the milk.
我得回教室去
Well, I'd better get back to class.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
不准动
Freeze!
不要
No!
No.
这是亨利舒普
This is Henry Shoop...
我未婚夫
my fiance.
你好
Hi.
你未婚夫？
Your fiance?
我未婚夫
Yeah, my fiance.
亨利
Henry, this is obviously my partner...
显然这是我的搭档 约翰金霸
John Kimble. Oh, jeez.
呃
Uh...
你好吗？
Hi. How you doing?
我拿个枕头 马上出来
Let me get this... and I'll be right out.
哦
Oh!
亲爱的 不要紧
It's okay, honey.
马上出来
I'll be right out.
我过生日
It's my birthday.
恭喜 谢谢
Well, congratulations.
他老远跑来令我惊喜
Thanks. He came up here just to surprise me.
还做了我爱吃的 意大利油面
And he made me my favorite... pasta a olio.
亨利 我爱你
I love you, Henry.
我爱你
I love you, too, Phoebes.
今夜要赶回去上班
Uh... Well, I've got to head back tonight. I've got to work.
亨利当厨师 我当厨师
Henry's a chef. I'm a chef.
你要嫁给厨师？手艺高超
You're marrying a chef? I'm marrying a great chef.
可想而知
That figures.
我的手艺好？真的？
You mean that, a great chef?
你是天才 不仅是手艺好？
Of course. You're a genius, Henry.
幸会
Not just a good chef?
恭喜 生日快乐
Well, nice to meet you. Congratulations. Happy birthday.
我喜欢 你不认为煮的太烂？
Thanks. You want some of this?
有韧性 正合我胃口
It wasn't overcooked? You're the best. It wasn't a little overcooked?
不 意大利面
No. Al dente.
柴克
Zach.
我是金霸 柴克的老师
Excuse me. I'm John Kimble, Zach's teacher.
他跟着来我不知道
I didn't know he was following me.
我对答录机留了话
Hi. I've been leaving messages on your machine.
我没有空回
I'm sorry. Things have been hectic.
现在呢？
What about now?
呃
Uh...
柴克 去散步 我和老师讲话
Go for a little walk. Your teacher and I have to talk.
呃
Uh...
我知道你要谈的事
I know what this is about.
你看到柴克腿上的瘀伤
I suppose you saw the bruises on Zach's legs?
三周以前我先生 接受精神治疗
My husband has started counseling about this. He's been going for three weeks now.
报告校方只会使事态严重
Please don't bring the school system into it. It will make matters worse.
他也打你？
He's beating you, too?
要不是他就医你会报告？
If he wasn't going to counseling... I could see the point of saying something...
相信再也不会发生
but I'm sure there won't be any more occurrences.
你不会说出去吧？
You won't say anything, will you?
拜托
Please?
他若再打人我要控告他
If he does it again, I press charges.
柴克
Zach.
有没有货？
You got the stuff?
谢了 伙计
Thanks, man.
你的货给她了 尾款在哪儿
Here, lady. I gave her your stuff. Where's the rest of my money?
老太太 你是谁？
Who are you, old lady?
你的神仙教母
Your fairy godmother.
进来
Come in.
调查一整天 柴克苏利文和克利
Hi. It took all day... but I found out Zach Sullivan and his mother...
非亲非故 我知道了
aren't related to Crisp. I just found out.
买一瓶酒供你约会用 不是约会 我晓得
Oh. I got a bottle of wine for your big date... It's not a date, I know.
但是别让乔伊丝起疑
But Joyce shouldn't think that.
这不太好吧
Thanks. I don't think it's a good idea.
为什么？
Why not?
违反平时的作风
Quickest way to slip up doing undercover work
会暴露密探身份
is doing things you normally wouldn't do.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你是说你赴女人的约会 一向不带美酒相赠？
You mean you wouldn't take wine to a woman who's invited you for dinner?
当然要带
Of course you would.
还要赠鲜花 拿去
And flowers as well. Here you go.
包她欢喜
She'll love them.
就是这里
Well, here we are.
哇塞 好漂亮
Wow. This is quite a place. They must be paying you
你的薪水比我多
a lot more than they're paying me.
但愿房子是我的
I wish it was my house.
朋友的房子
It belongs to a friend of mine.
他让我们住 我们负责维护
After the divorce, he said we could stay here
你的朋友真好
in exchange for keeping the place up.
是的
You must have nice friends.
菜马上就好
Yes, I do. Dinner won't be ready for a few minutes.
能否生个火？
Can you start a fire?
这个好办
It shouldn't be a problem.
我带你去拿柴
I'll show you where the wood is.
好
All right!
跟我来
Come on. Come on!
在这儿
Right here.
钻进去
In here.
这是我躲藏的密窟
This is my secret hiding spot.
哇塞 了不起
Wow. This is amazing.
我亲手盖的
I made it myself. What's this?
这是什么？当心 强力死光炮
Don't touch that! It's a laser...
好 我当心
and it'll burn a hole right through you.
不要开枪
Okay. I'll be careful. Oh, don't shoot.
-嘣 嘣… - 不要开枪
- Boom! Boom! - Don't shoot.
架死光枪保卫我们
I put up these lasers to protect us.
防什么？
To protect you from what?
防坏人
The bad people.
要不要看别的？
Do you want to see something else?
走
Come on.
看什么？
What?
看到了吗？
See that?
你是说发波台？
You mean the tower?
我要在天线上架一座死光炮
I'm going to plant one of my lasers on that antenna.
不过要在夜里进行
But I'll have to do it at night.
要不然坏人会知道位置
Otherwise the bad people will know where it is.
最后上桌的是烂香蕉
Last one to the table is a rotten banana!
你们男生开心吧？
Have you guys had fun?
我马上出来
Yeah. Be right out!
你进来干什么？
What you doing in there?
我很失落
I'm lost.
迷路了 餐室在那儿？房子太大
Where is the dining room? This house is huge.
- 傻子 跟我来 - 呼
- Follow me, silly. - Whew.
你们的照片很漂亮
These are beautiful pictures of you and Dominic.
谢谢你
Thank you.
多明尼说你有个儿子
When I was putting Dominic to bed... he mentioned you had a son, too.
是的 不过我离婚了
That's right. But I'm divorced.
幸运的是前妻再嫁了好老公
I'm lucky. My ex got remarried to a very nice man.
他对我儿很好
He's really good to my son.
我可以常看他
I see him a lot.
你的前夫
What about your ex-husband?
有没有常来看多明尼
Does he see Dominic a lot?
没有
Uh, no.
离婚之后他回法国了
After the divorce, he moved back to France.
教育孩子和赡养费呢？
What about child support and alimony?
他是否供给？
Does he take care of you?
对不起 我问到隐私
I'm sorry about being so personal.
他走我就高兴了不求他供养
I was so glad to see him go I didn't worry about that part.
多明尼记不得他 这样最好
Dominic doesn't even remember him. I prefer it that way.
真是这样？
Are you sure?
是的
Yeah.
为何问起？
Why?
多明尼跟我谈到
Well, Dominic was talking to me about having to move around a lot
常常迁移躲避坏人
to keep the bad people away.
坏人？
Bad people? Something about having to leave
他谈到半夜离家
in the middle of the night
丢下玩具
and leave his toys behind.
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
我以为他忘了
I thought he'd forgotten about that.
对不起 我无意提伤心事
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to upset you.
不能怪你
It's not your fault.
我的前夫是活生生的梦魇
The truth is, my ex-husband is a walking nightmare.
他没弃我们 是我们弃他
He didn't leave us, we left him.
他曾找到我们要带多明尼走
He found out where we were and tried to kidnap Dominic.
现在他不知我们下落
He doesn't know where we are now...
我要保持这样
and I'd like to keep it that way.
当然
Of course.
幸亏他在法国
I'm glad he's in France
不是在附近
and doesn't live nearby.
他不是在法国
He doesn't live in France.
在法国是对多明尼说的
I told Dominic that he lived in France.
结婚之初我不了解他的为人
I didn't know who my ex-husband was when I married him.
当时年轻愚昧走错了
I was young and stupid, and I made a mistake.
我不要连累多明尼
I don't want Dominic to pay for it.
这段往事这儿的人都不知道
Look, nobody around here knows anything about this.
我居然对你说出来
I can't even believe I told you.
答应我不告诉别人
You have to promise me you won't tell anyone.
你可以信赖我
You can trust me.
这是非常好的 完美的
That's very good. Perfect.
玛莉 我们再试 你先
Okay. Let's try it again. Mary, you first.
八十七年以前
Fourscores and seven years ago.
我们的祖先…
Our forefathers brought...
四个祖宗？
Four fathers?
老师 林肯有四个爸爸？
Mr. Kimble, did Lincoln have four fathers?
我有三个爸
Uh... I had three fathers...
一个叫华德 二个叫雷夫
One named Walt, two named Ralph.
林肯可有四个母亲？
Did Lincoln have four mothers?
他有二个母亲 第一个先死
As a matter of fact, he had two mothers. Unfortunately, the first one died.
我就知道
I knew it.
好 休息一下 听话
Um... Okay. Let's take a break. Come on.
你们给我绕圈走
I want you to walk around in a circle. Go.
绕 快点
Start. Come on.
乔伊丝的"房事"无误
Well, Joyce's story about the house checked out.
滑雪季节屋主才来住两周
It belongs to a guy who only uses it during the ski season.
她有一千元存款
She's got under $1,000 in the bank...
没租保管箱
no stocks, no bonds,
她的本名之下别无恒产
no other assets under the name Joyce Paulmarie.
薪水比我少 真可怜
Her teacher's salary is less than mine, which is pathetic.
再查 调查可有国外户头
Keep looking. Check for offshore accounts under Dominic's name...
她的生活不像是有几百万元的人
She doesn't live like someone with millions of dollars.
她不像这类人
She doesn't even seem the type.
金霸 可能不是她
Kimble, this might not be her.
一定是她
It's got to be her.
为什么？
Why? Because she doesn't want to have
因为她同前夫恩断义绝？
anything to do with her ex-husband?
我知道是她
I know it's her.
可知我的看法？
Know what I think?
你指望就是她
You want it to be her.
你真心喜欢她 所以吓得要死
You really like her, and it's scaring you.
对不起 意外吧
Excuse me! Surprise!
各位女士 出乎意表
Ladies! Ladies, surprise.
显然我不擅长烘制蛋糕
Obviously, I'm not into baking cakes...
所以我捐这个作摸彩奖品
so I brought these little things to donate for the raffle prizes.
那女人是谁？
Who the hell is that?
我跟你提的女人
She's the one I was telling you about.
她老公跟男人私奔
Her husband ran away with another guy.
令她很难受
It's been terrible for her.
你不是心软了吧？
You're not getting mellow on me, are you?
齐步走 一 二 三 四
3, 4. 1, 2, 3... Hi.
来吧 一 二 三 四
Come on. 1, 2, 3, 4.
走呀
Come on. Go, go.
今年要你的班朗诵 盖茨堡宣言
I see they stuck you with the Gettysburg Address this year.
不错
They sure did.
部队 立定
Company, halt!
庵
Um...
昨夜的事
About last night...
我仔细想过
I've been thinking about it, and...
对你说出来我很高兴
I'm glad I told you all those things.
我也高兴
So am I.
我得走了
Um... I-I better get going.
我也得走了
Yeah. I have to get going, too.
一切顺利吧
Is everything okay?
是呀
Yeah.
明天同乐会见
See you tomorrow at the fair.
我盼望明天
I'm looking forward to it.
你看什么？
What are you looking at? Ha ha ha!
嘘
Shh!
齐步走 一 二 三 四
March! 1, 2, 3, 4.
我同那位老师讲话 如此而已
I was just talking to the teacher, that's all.
不要笑
Yeah. Don't laugh.
我以你们光荣 前进
Okay. I'm proud of you. Keep going.
柴克迟到 抱歉 车子抛锚
I'm sorry Zach's late. The car wouldn't start.
要听话 我爱你
You be a good boy. I love you.
嘿 冠军
Hi, champ. Oh!
怎么回事？
What's the matter?
不像话
Oh, no.
我又跌跤了
I fell down again.
喂 等一下
Hey, wait a minute.
呃
Uh...
地窖门没关 害柴克摔下去
I forgot to close the door to the basement...
医生说不要紧
and Zach had a bad fall.
老说摔倒 没有新解的词儿？
You all say the same thing, "He fell down."
事实如此
Don't you have anything better to say?
我不必向你解释
I don't have to justify myself to you!
你没资格质问我
You have no right talking to me like that.
一定是金霸先生 久仰
How are you doing? You must be the Mr. Kimble we hear so much about.
You must be the Mr. Kimble we hear so much about.
你打小孩 我打你
You hit the kid, I hit you.
你浑帐
You bastard!
你不值我动手
You're not worth it.
我要告你虐待儿童
I'm pressing charges against you.
对不起 借光
Excuse me, everybody.
对不起 我不该当着同学打他
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have hit the man... especially in front of the children.
这是我的错
It was a mistake.
我查过你的底细
I checked you out.
你没有在学校任教的资历
There is no record of you ever having taught at any public school...
在加州或别处都没有
in California or anywhere else.
金霸先生 你没有教学经验对不对？
Mr. Kimble... you have no teaching experience whatsoever, do you?
总算有人察觉
Someone finally noticed.
带雪貂来不应该
I thought the introduction of a ferret was a horrible idea...
不过孩子都喜欢
but the children seemed to like it.
你用哨子指挥学童太离谱
I thought the use of your police whistle was outrageous...
只有这法子
That's all I could think of.
拜托 让我说完
Please allow me to finish.
对不起
Sorry.
不过方法管用
But it worked.
你是什么样的警察 我不清楚
I have no idea what kind of police officer you are...
不过却是优秀的老师
but you're a very good teacher.
谢谢你
Thank you.
请你告诉我 不要撒谎
Now, will you tell me something? Don't lie.
揍那个浑帐东西的 感觉如何？
What did it feel like to hit that son of a bitch?
很痛快
It felt great.
呀
Yeah.
明天早上 早点来上课
Well, tomorrow morning. Bright and early.
谢谢你
Thank you. Yeah.
对 就是她
Yeah, that's her. And there goes our goddamn case.
我们的案子泡汤了
Tell O'Hara and Kimble their witness is dead...
通知金霸他们 克利要出来了
so Crisp is going to walk.
召他们回来 其他案子很多
We want them back here. We've got lots of other cases to clear.
他们认为找到逃妻了
O'Hara says they think they've located the wife.
钱呢？
And the money?
正在调查
They're looking into it.
放屁
Have them tell the wife
叫他们通知逃妻克利 知其下落
we're letting Crisp go, and he knows where she is.
若要警方保护 就得交出脏款
If she wants police protection, she'll produce the money.
耽误救你 抱歉
Sorry it took so long, Cullen.
气色很好
Hey, you're looking great.
妈 我爱你
I love you, Mother.
我们全家快团圆了
We're going to be a family again, son.
"爱莎莉亚同乐会"
起跑
Go!
八十七年以前
Fourscore and seven years ago Fourscore and seven years ago
我们的祖先在这新大陆…
our forefathers brought forth on this continent ...
建立新国家
a new nation a new nation
生于自由理念
conceived in liberty conceived in liberty
为人人生而平等的主张
and dedicated to the proposition and dedicated to the proposition
献身奋斗
that all men are created equal that all men are created equal
而致力维护
and that government and that government
民有 民治
of the people by the people
民享的政府
and for the people
不坠于世
shall not perish from this earth.
谢谢各位
Thank you very much.
我来介绍 我们的幼稚园老师
Oh! I'd like to introduce you to our kindergarten teacher.
他是来代课
He came to us as a substitute teacher...
他的表现证明 他的价值非凡
and he's proven to be a wonderful asset.
欢迎他来我们的社区
Let's welcome him into our community
但愿他考虑永久居留
and hope that he considers staying on a permanent basis.
各位女士先生
Ladies and gentlemen...
约翰金霸先生
Mr. John Kimble.
好城镇
Nice town. Hmm.
空气新鲜
Ahh! Smell that fresh air.
我们应该在这里置产
We should think about buying something up here...
买一栋滨湖的森林木屋
like some log cabin in the woods near a lake.
小孩喜欢户外活动
Kids love that outdoor kind of stuff.
我到药房去
I'll be in the pharmacy.
不要惹事生非
Try not to step in anything.
我帮你挑选 玩具赛车卖完了
I'd like to help you. But we're pretty much out of the race cars... unless...
只剩这套样品
This is the last one.
它的造型仍旧这么棒
It's still in great shape.
情况很好 我给你打九折
If you don't mind waiting, I'll wrap it up.
今天你走运 我加倍跟你买
I'll knock 10% off... I have a better idea. I'll pay you twice what he's charging.
我答应给儿子要这个
I promised my boy I'd get him one.
抱歉 我儿子要这个
I'd love to help you... but my kid's been bugging me since Christmas.
我出四倍钱跟你买
I'll pay you four times what it's worth. Get your kid something even better.
抱歉 能不能包装？当然可以
Sorry. Can you gift-wrap it?
我出高价没有恶意
Hanna, could you wrap that, please? No harm in trying.
观光客
Tourists.
多明尼 很好
Great, Dominic. You're doing well.
我在这边等你
I'll wait over here for you, okay?
好
Okay.
天气真好
Great day, huh?
时间紧迫
We've run out of time.
要对乔伊丝施压力
We've got to press Joyce now.
为什么？
What do you mean?
昨夜仙蒂死了
Cindy O.D.'d last night.
可恶
Shit.
克利获释 可能已前来此地
They released Crisp this morning. He's probably on his way here.
组长要我转告你
Salazar said if Joyce is Crisp's wife...
若乔伊丝是克利之妻
she's got to cooperate about the money...
交出脏款 否则警方不会保护她
or she gets no police protection.
浑蛋
Bastard.
乌苏拉 你好吗？
Ursula, how are you?
什么事？
What?
我要跟你说实话
I've got to tell you the truth.
她不叫乌苏拉
Her name's not Ursula.
不是我妹子
She's not my sister.
什么？
I beg your pardon?
不是你以为的身份
We're not who you think we are.
什么意思？
What is this?
我们是警察
We're police officers.
瑞雪 我们知道你的身份
We know who you are... Rachel.
开玩笑
This is a joke, right?
不是 你卷三百万元潜逃
No. This is no joke. You took $3 million.
你弄错
I think...
克利知道你的下落 他要来
Crisp knows where you are. He could be here any minute.
多明尼呢？
Where's Dominic?
作证可以免罪
You'll get immunity for your testimony...
但你要帮警方
but we need you to help us.
多明尼呢？
Where's Dominic?
在骑马 你得说出钱的下落
On a pony. We'll offer protection if you tell us about the money.
浑帐 没有钱
There's no money, you son of a bitch.
根本没有
There never was!
不公平 我没骑完
No, it's not fair! I'm not finished yet!
坏人找上我们了
The bad people have found us.
怎么会没钱？
What do you mean, " no money"?
为什么对老师生气？
Why are you mad at Mr. Kimble?
他愚蠢
Because he's a jerk.
让我帮助你
Please let me help you!
不要烦我
Leave me alone!
等一下
Joyce, wait! Wait!
要是你没卷款
If you didn't take the money...
他要你干什么？
why is he after you?
不是要我 他要多明尼
He doesn't want me. He wants Dominic.
她又要逃亡了
She's going to run again.
对
Yeah.
除非我们助她
Unless we do something about it.
对
Yeah.
喂 别发呆了
Hey, snap out of it!
达里尔 达里尔
Daryl. Daryl.
我再给你机会
I'm sorry. I wanted to give you a second chance.
两百元现钞
200, cash.
你怎么搞的？
What is wrong with you?
我的话你听不懂？
I'm still not getting through to you, am I, Daryl?
我给二世意外之礼
Mother, got this great surprise for Junior.
57元9角
That'll be 57.90.
57.90.
儿童用阿斯匹灵 活血剂
Children's aspirin, children's decongestant...
抗敏感
antihistamine.
"直肠体温计"
体温计？
A thermometer?
感冒流行对不对？
A lot of flu going around, right?
正是流行季节
It is the season.
儿子没有病
The boy's not sick.
我是预防
Doesn't hurt to take precautions.
妈 你会害他生病
Mother, you are going to make him sick.
多年来我都没事 你却逼我吃药
You stuffed all this crap into me, and nothing was wrong.
因为吃药才没事儿
That's why there was nothing wrong with you.
怎么说得过你？
Now, how can you argue with that?
乔伊丝
Joyce!
乔伊丝 多明尼
Joyce! Dominic!
浑帐 多明尼呢？
You bastard! Where's Dominic?
我不知道
I don't know. What happened?
你引他来 小孩若丢了我跟你拚了
You led him here. If he has Dominic, I'll kill you.
住手
Stop it!
放开我
Let go of me!
会找到他 别胡闹
We'll find him. Stop it.
会找到他
We'll find him.
多明尼
Dominic!
他走之前说过什么？
Did he say anything before he left?
说什么去拿死光
He said something about getting his lasers.
死光？
Lasers?
我也许知道下落
I think I know where he is.
啊哈 帮帮我
Aah! Help!
救命
Help! Help!
来人呀 救命
Somebody! Help!
多明尼 别动
Hold on!
当心
I'll get him down.
救命
Help!
不要动 我来了
Hold on. I'm right here.
孩子 别动
Good boy. All right. Just hold on.
抱紧我
Okay. Just hold on.
很好 好
Oh, good. Okay.
我想在天线上架死光炮
I was going to put the lasers in the antenna.
我知道 不必耽心了
I know. Don't worry about anything now.
我抱你 抱紧我 抱紧
I got you. Just hold on tight now. Hold on tight, okay?
很好
Good.
若失掉多明尼 只怕我活不下去
If I lost Dominic... I don't think I could go on living.
你不会失掉他
You're not going to lose him.
是吗？
That's right. I'm not.
孤冷放风声说我卷款 诱使流氓混混找我好领赏
Cullen said I stole his money so these creeps would follow us for a reward.
你不了解他
You don't know what he's like. Oh, yes, I do.
我了解他
I know him well.
所以不让他接近你和多明尼
That's why I don't want him to get you two.
你或别人我都信不过
Can't trust you or anybody.
你可以信赖我 你说过这话
You can trust me. That's what you said before.
结果你竟然是警察
And you turned out to be a cop.
我
I...
我无心伤害你
I didn't mean to hurt you.
真希望我是老师
I wish I was a kindergarten teacher...
可惜不是
but I'm not.
我是警察 只懂得办案子
I'm a cop. That's all I know how to be.
我要离开
I have to get out of here.
你有儿子
You have a son.
换了你也会逃走
If you were me, you'd do the same thing.
我已有七年没见儿子
I have a son I've hardly seen in seven years.
我在他心中没分量
I don't mean anything to him.
前妻再婚 不要我干扰她的生活
My ex-wife got remarried. She doesn't want me to be part of his life.
我的家破了
I lost my family.
我不该任其破裂
I should never have let it happen.
为什么跟我说这些？
Why are you telling me all of this?
我不愿失去你
I don't want to lose you.
不愿失去多明尼
I don't want to lose Dominic.
我立誓让你不必再逃避他
I swear you'll never have to run from him again.
放心 我们就在墙那边
Don't worry about anything, okay? We're going to be right across the hall.
一切都好 我们只是小心起见
Everything's going to be fine. We just want to be extra careful.
别耽忧
Thanks. Don't worry.
喔
Whoo!
好 安静
All right, all right. Settle down.
早安
Good morning.
早安 金霸老师
Good morning, Mr. Kimble.
坐下
Sit down.
又见大家很高兴
It's very nice to see you all again.
见过我的好友菲比
Meet my very good friend, Phoebe O'Hara.
早安 菲比
Good morning, Phoebe.
菲比小姐要跟大家讲要紧事
Miss O'Hara is going to talk to you about something very important.
大家专心听她讲话
So pay attention to what she has to say, okay?
记住 不要怕
Remember, no fear.
谢谢
Thanks.
呀？
Yeah?
男生有小鸡鸡 女生有小屁屁
Boys have a penis. Girls have a vagina.
你教基本性知识 这很重要
Well, you taught them the basics. That's important.
好吧 现在…
Okay, now...
我们来讲真正重要的
today we're going to talk about something else that's really important.
今天来谈谈陌生人
Today we're going to talk about strangers.
在家里若有生人敲门
If a stranger knocks on your door...
不要应门
never answer the door.
因为不理陌生人
Because we never talk to strangers.
我们一起说一遍
Let's say that together.
我们决不理睬陌生人
We never talk to strangers. Right.
可不可以理睬陌生小孩？
Can we talk to kids?
可以 同小孩讲话没关系
Yeah, it's okay. You can talk to kids.
同狗讲话呢？
What about dogs?
咦？
Huh?
可不可以同狗讲话？
Can we talk to dogs?
你可以同狗讲话
Yeah, you can talk to dogs.
不可以的是
But what you can't do...
决不可以 决不 决不
what you must never ever do is...
决不理睬陌生人
never talk to strangers.
在幼教方面 本校强调3C信条
On the kindergarten level... we try to emphasize the three C's:
关怀 礼貌 勇气
Caring, courtesy and courage.
勇气也是我的信条
Courage. That's my philosophy, too.
葛先生 你是单亲？
Are you a single parent, Mr. Green?
不是 太太在后 处理卖房子事宜
No, my wife had to stay behind to complete the sale of our home.
迁来之前 她要我探视学校情形
I'm checking the schools before we buy a home here.
幼稚园生多数不识字
Most kindergarten children can't read yet.
我儿识字
My son can.
六岁就识字？很好
He reads at 6? That's good.
还会写字 我教他
And writes. I taught him myself.
他好像很特别
He sounds like a special child.
是的 他运动也很行
He is. He's a great athlete.
幼稚园在这里 请看
Here's what you've waited for. The kindergarten. Have a look.
多明尼 多明尼是群山之王
Oh, Dominic, Dominic... Dominic is king of the mountain!
多明尼 加油
Way to go, Dominic.
恭喜 多明尼 群山之王
Here's your crown. Congratulations, Dominic. The king of Mount Kimble!
多明尼
Dominic.
他长相粗粗却是好老师
He looks odd, but he's a wonderful teacher.
是 我相信
Yes, I'm sure he is.
看到孤冷二世没有？
Did you see Cullen Jr.?
看到了
Yeah, yeah.
他叫多明尼
She calls him Dominic. She'd always wanted to name him Dominic.
她喜欢起这名字 好驴
What a dumb name.
雪茄熄掉 损小孩健康
Put that cigar out. It's unhealthy for the kid.
然后你开着飞机冲入云霄
Then you make your aeroplane go up into the clouds.
去看看
Check it out.
右
Right.
要冷静 火警演习
Okay, stay calm. Okay, it's probably a fire drill.
哦 伙计
Oh, man.
金霸 走道里浓烟密布
Kimble, the hallway's full of smoke.
好 火警演习
Okay, this is a fire drill. Come on.
快走 真有火警
This is the real thing.
照练习队形
Just the way we practiced.
成两路队形出去
Go out there.
快走 照练习的队形
Fast. Just the way we practiced it.
来吧
Come on.
洒水 不要怕
It's only water. Don't be scared.
贴近墙壁 我们走吧
Stay close to the wall. Let's go.
来吧 来吧
Come on. Come on.
多明尼 紧跟着我
Dominic, stay close to me, okay?
跟着我 不要走散
Stay close to me.
留在我后面
Stay behind me.
不要走散了
Don't get separated.
啊哈
Aah!
你好吗？起来
Are you all right? Come on. Let's go.
多明尼 等一下
Dominic, wait!
多明尼
Dominic!
救命 来人呀
Help! Somebody help me!
救命
Help!
有陌生人
Stranger!
陌生人
陌生人 陌生人
Stranger! Stranger! Stranger! Stranger!
多明尼？
Dominic! Where's Dominic?
上楼 我照顾小孩
Dominic!
啊哈
Aah!
跟上 跟上
Okay, stay together. Stay together.
跟上 抓住同伴
Stay together. Hold onto your partner.
不要脱队 牵我的手 跟上
Okay, don't lag behind. Hold onto my hand. Stay together.
多明尼呢？
Where's Dominic?
在里面 金霸去找他了
He's inside. Kimble's looking for him. Joyce!
乔伊斯
Joyce!
救命
Help!
不要怕 我不伤你 我不伤你
It's okay. It's okay. I'm not going to hurt you. I'm not going to hurt you.
不要怕
It's okay.
我是消防员 专门救人
I'm a fireman. I help people.
你的头盔呢？
Well, where's your hat?
头盔？
My hat?
反应快我喜欢
I love this.
骗不过自己的儿子 他才六岁
I can't fool my own boy. He's just 6 years old.
你问得好 我不是消防员
You're right. I'm no jerk fireman.
我有事告诉你
I'm going to tell you something, Dominic.
这件事你很难了解 不过
It's going to be hard for you to understand...
你得相信我
but you got to believe me.
我是你爸爸
I'm your father, Dominic.
你的父亲
Your father.
你不认得我了？
Don't you recognize me?
不认得
No.
当然认得
Sure you do. It's me.
你忘了 "一闪一闪亮晶晶" ？
Don't you remember Twinkle, twinkle, little star?
你看 我们的手形状一样
We have the same kind of hands.
你不记得了？
Don't you remember?
你不是我爸 他住在法国
You're not my father. My father lives in France.
你妈说的？不是真话
Your mother told you that... but that's not true!
我是你爸 找你五年了
I'm your father! I've been searching for you for five years.
救命
Help! Help!
我是你爸 你要相信我要听话
Dominic, I'm your father. You're going to have to do what I say. Do you understand?
不准动
Freeze!
你们不知道有火警？
Don't you know there's a fire?
我们以为是演习
We thought it was another drill.
出去
Well, get out!
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
等一下 里面失火
Whoa, honey. That's a fire in there.
我要进去
I got a kid in there.
不行
NO way!
我是警察 如要抽掉罚单我找你帮忙
I'm a cop. If I need a ticket fixed, I'll call you.
别为难
In the meantime, stay out.
出去 走
Go on.
好吧
All right.
安静 听到没有？
Quiet, you hear me? Quiet.
不
No!
瑞雪
Rachel!
真会添麻烦
Let go! Just what I need.
孤冷 请你放了他
Please, let him go. Let him go!
怎么出去？
How the hell do you get out of here?
请你别这样
Please, please, don't do this!
你吓坏他了
You're scaring him!
吓他？他当然怕
Scared? Of course he's scared.
我的事你瞒着他
You told him lies about me.
害得他不认我
My son doesn't know me because of you.
听我说 听着
Listen! Just listen.
你自我身边偷走他
You stole him from me!
把他还给我
Please, give him back.
不要碰他
Don't touch him!
多明尼 我必须动手
Aah! Dominic, I had to do it!
我不愿意 她逼我动手
I didn't want to do it. She made me.
一切都会好
Everything's going to be okay, Dominic.
多明尼？
Dominic? Come back.
回来 我们逃出去
We're getting out of here.
多明尼
Dominic?
我们重组新家庭
Going to start a whole new family.
啊哈
Aah!
多明尼
Dominic!
抓到你了
Gotcha!
我真的爱你知道吗
I love you. Do you understand?
跟我说你明白 说呀
Tell me you understand that. Say it. Say it!
我明白
I understand.
叫爸
Daddy.
爸爸
金霸 站住
Hold it! Right there.
弃械 快点
Drop it! Hurry!
弃械 他不是人质 是你儿子
Don't. Don't. He's not your hostage. He's your son.
枪丢在地上
Drop it. On the floor.
你拿枪威胁亲生儿子？
You'll do this to your own son?
弃械 我要失控了 快
Drop it! I'm losing it! Hurry!
别激动 我弃械
Relax. I'm putting it down.
快点
Hurry!
枪在这儿
Here it is.
Here it is. Just don't harm the boy, okay?
好 这才识相
Good. Good. That's smart.
好吧
All right.
现在放小孩走
Why don't you let the boy go now?
孩子是我的 他是我儿
The boy is mine! He's my boy!
找你自己的家人
You get your own goddamn family!
啊哈
Aah!
不
No!
你好吗？
Are you okay?
还好 去找多明尼
I'm okay. Get Dominic. Okay.
多明尼
Dominic!
我的孙子呢？
Where's my grandson?
不知道
I don't know.
我的孙子呢？
Where's my grandson?
你去死吧
Go to hell.
你才要死 浑帐
That's where you're going, you son of a bitch!
没有汽车你也不堪一击
You're not so tough without your car... are you?
金霸先生 你好吗？
Mr. Kimble, are you all right?
我厌恶吃凉粉
Oh, I hate this.
不要 他不吃
Nah, he doesn't want to eat that.
他是硬汉
He's a tough guy.
硬汉不吃凉粉
Tough guys don't eat Jell-O.
回头我再来
I'll come back later.
你觉得如何？
Hi. Hi. How you feeling?
好多了 你呢？
Much better. How about you?
死不了 快出院 这玩艺倒胃
I'll live. Check out of here. This stuff will kill you.
别吐得我一身
Just don't throw up on me.
不会吐得你一身
I'm not going to throw up on you...
但我要亲你
but I am going to kiss you.
菲比
Phoebe.
谢谢你救我
Thanks.
谢谢 伙计
Thanks, partner.
没什么
Sure.
大家好 我带了好东西来
How's everybody feeling today? I brought goodies. Did I do that?
鲜花给我
Give me the flowers.
我有好东西
I got some goodies and...
勾住了 我为你做的菜
I got it caught. And something I cooked myself.
亨利
Henry
你穿了衣服我没认出来
I almost didn't recognize you with all your clothes on.
你的气色很好
You look good yourself.
啊哈
Aah!
请他参加婚礼
Did I... I'm sorry. The wedding.
呀 呃
Yeah. Uh...
我们结婚请赏光
You're coming to the wedding, right?
安不安全？
Is it safe?
你们的婚礼我决不错过
I wouldn't miss this for the world.
那么
So...
请帖寄到那里？
where do we send the invitation?
嗯？
Hmm?
都交给你了
They're all yours.
小朋友 好
Hi, kids.
金霸老师
Mr. Kimble!
我回来了
I'm back.
耶
Yay!
没有加入工会 直到
Didn't join the union until...
各位同学 失陪
Class, excuse me.
他们要做羞羞脸的事
Uh-oh. They're going to do it.